AMDA — Verify Before You Pay
Track 1 scores accuracy first, then ranks by tokens spent.
Local tokens are free.
So the scarce resource isn't capability —
it's confidence in a free answer.
AMDA verifies before it escalates: code is executed,
math is re-derived, logic is solved independently.
Only a genuine verification failure calls a paid
remote model — throttled and capped.
Live run: the exact image pushed to GHCR,
under the real 2 vCPU / 4GB grading constraint.
5 of 8 tasks resolved locally — zero token cost.
Only 3 tasks escalated — 33 output tokens, total.
228-task internal benchmark. Math: 28/28 once verified.
Logic: 92% solver accuracy.
We read real competitor code. No one else
re-derives answers before spending a paid token.
Verify locally. Escalate surgically.
Spend only where correctness demands it.
AMDA — built for AMD Developer Hackathon Act II, Track 1.